(upbeat music)
(rain pouring)
(singer vocalizing)
♪ You were my sun ♪
♪ You were my Earth ♪
♪ But you didn't know all
the ways I loved you, no ♪
♪ So you took a chance ♪
♪ And made other plans ♪
♪ But I bet you didn't think ♪
♪ That they would come crashing down, no ♪
♪ You don't have to say, what you did ♪
♪ I already know, I found out from him ♪
♪ Now there's just no chance ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ There'll never be ♪
♪ And don't it make you sad about it ♪
♪ You told me you love me ♪
♪ Why did you leave me all alone ♪
♪ Now you tell me you need me ♪
♪ When you call me on the phone ♪
♪ Girl, I refuse ♪
♪ You must have me confused
with some other guy ♪
♪ The bridges were burned ♪
♪ Now it's your turn to cry ♪
♪ Cry me a river ♪
♪ Cry me a river, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You know that they say ♪
♪ That some things are
better left unsaid ♪
♪ And it wasn't like you only
talked to him and you know it ♪
♪ Don't act like you don't know it ♪
♪ And all of these things people told me ♪
♪ Keep messin' with my
head, messin' with my head ♪
♪ Should've picked honesty ♪
♪ Then you may not have blown it, yeah ♪
♪ You don't have to
say, don't have to say ♪
♪ What you did, what you did ♪
♪ I already know, I already know ♪
♪ I found out from him, uh ♪
♪ Now there's just no chance, no chance ♪
♪ For you and me, you and me ♪
♪ There'll never be ♪
♪ Don't it make you sad about it ♪
♪ You told me you love me ♪
♪ Why did you leave me
all alone, all alone ♪
♪ Now you tell me you need me ♪
♪ When you call me on the phone ♪
♪ Girl, I refuse ♪
♪ You must have me confused
with some other guy ♪
♪ I'm not like them, baby ♪
♪ The bridges were burned ♪
♪ Now it's your turn,
it's your turn to cry ♪
♪ So cry me a river, go on and just ♪
♪ Cry me a river, go on and just ♪
♪ Cry me a river, baby, go on and just ♪
♪ Cry me a river, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ The damage is done, so
I guess I be leaving ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ The damage is done, so
I guess I be leaving ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ The damage is done, so
I guess I be leaving ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ The damage is done, so
I guess I be, leaving ♪
♪ You don't have to say,
you don't have to say ♪
♪ What you did, what you did ♪
♪ I already know, I already know ♪
♪ I found out from him, uh ♪
♪ Now there's just no chance, no chance ♪
♪ For you and me, you and me ♪
♪ There'll never be ♪
♪ Don't it make you sad about it ♪
♪ Cry me a river, go on and just ♪
♪ Cry me a river, baby, go on and just ♪
♪ Cry me a river, you can go on and just ♪
♪ Cry me a river, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Cry me a river, baby, go on and just ♪
♪ Cry me a river, go on and just ♪
♪ Cry me a river, come on baby, cry ♪
♪ Cry me a river, I don't
wanna cry no more, yeah yeah ♪
♪ Cry me a river ♪
♪ Cry me a river, oh ♪
♪ Cry me a river, cry me, cry me, oh ♪
♪ Cry me a river, cry me, cry me ♪
(upbeat music)